ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL

rohitmandal66225@gmail.com

7543895659

linkedin.com/in/gordxrohit

https://gordxrohitdemo.netlify.app/

Summary

SELF-TAUGHT FRONTEND DEVELOPER | 2YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN WEB DEVELOPMENT |
CONTENT CREATOR AT DCODER MOBILE APP | #1 AT DCODER MOBILE APP WORLD WIDE | 40+ WEB
DEVELOPMENT PROJECT MADE AT DCODER APP | 1900+ STARS RECEIVED AND 1600+ FORKED BY
PEOPLE

Experience

/> Content Creator

Dcoder

May 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

POSTING PROJECTS RELATED WEBDEVELOPMENT

- > USING HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT
- > FOR HELPING ASPIRING DEVELOPER
- > MADE 40+ PROJECTS
- > STAR RECIVED 1900+
- > FORK BY PEOPLE -1600+

User Interface Designer

Figma

Mar 2022 - Present (7 months +)

Developing UI Mockups FOR MOBILE

Developing UI Working Prototype Based Mockup Like :-

- > YOUTUBE MUSIC
- > MESSENGER CLONE APP
- > WHATSAPP CLONE APP

Web Designer

Self Employed

May 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

Web Development Projects Building

- > Started Posting My Web Development Projects Posting on Dcoder Mobile app as a journey or for helping Aspiring Developer
- > Html
- > CSS
- > Javascript

Education

St. Thomas High School

10th (CBSE), Matriculation

Matriculation Done From ST. THOMAS HIGH SCHOOL (Dhanbad) Jharkhand

Government Polytechnic Kharsawan

Diploma in Computer Engineering , Computer Engineering Sep 2019 - Jul 2022 Diploma in Computer Engineering with 86.75 %

Licenses & Certifications

Python & Data Science - LetsUpgrade ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL

Web Development - Kunal i technology ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL

- **Javascript Programming Essential Bootcamp** LetsUpgrade ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S HTML Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S CSS Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- Javascript Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S Responsive web design Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S Java Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- SQL Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S Php Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- Same Development with Javascript Sololearn

ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL

- **S jQuery** Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- Web Development Fundamentals Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- Sololearn
- **C programming** Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- S React + Redux Sololearn
 ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- G Coding for Marketers Sololearn ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL
- **Python & Data Science** LetsUpgrade ROHIT KUMAR MANDAL

Skills

Figma (Software) • Web Design • Front-End Development • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Video Editing • User Experience (UX) • User Interface Design